Blair Warner

blairthedesigner.com blairthedesigner@gmail.com

Hi, I'm Blair. I have been putting people first for over 13 years as a User Experience Designer, User Interface Designer, Graphic Designer and educator. I like encountering new problems and working with others to find solutions to them. I also enjoy coffee, drawing, music, making things, and wear too much indigo and denim.

Experience

UX/UI Designer Binfinity 1.2018 - 7.2021

I worked on all levels of design, from ideation to final output for a company in the cryptocurrency space. I worked closely with members of a multidisciplinary team applying user-centered design principles to web and mobile applications.

UX Designer Fusion Systems Group 5.2017 - 12.2017

I worked on a web based restaurant management software suite in an Agile development environment. I worked closely with stakeholders, developers and lead UX designer applying user-centered design principles to the project.

Freelance UX/UI Designer Blair the Designer 8.2016 - 5.2017

I provided clients with user experience and interface design solutions that met both user needs and business goals. I worked with product managers, developers and other designers to create user-centered designs on web, iOS and Android platforms.

Instructional Assistant (UX Design) General Assembly 11.2016 - 2.2017 I assisted instructors with curriculum creation, lesson planning, and student evaluations. I planned a cross-functional hackathon.

English Teacher 4.2006 - 3.2008 / 4.2011 - 3.2016

I worked in a total of twenty-two different elementary and junior high schools in the Greater Tokyo area. I collaborated with teachers to make lessons and activities tailored to different grades and skill levels. I acted as a cultural ambassador for my students. I participated in school functions and after school activities.

Graphic Designer / Letterpress Printer Bell'Invito Stationers 2.2009 - 8.2009 I worked with clients, marketers, designers and printers to develop custom, couture letterpress stationery. I was also responsible for the creation of web graphics for the company website, and file preparation for die creation. I also operated 19th-century letterpresses for printing and die-cutting, as well as assembly of stationery.

Assistant Graphic Designer Standard Deluxe, Inc. 5.2005 - 2.2006

I worked with clients, designers and printers to create designs for silk screen printing. I worked with web developers to create web graphics and input data for the company website and web store.

Education

UX Design Immersive General Assembly 2016

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Graphic Design Auburn University 2000 - 2005

Research Methods

Affinity Diagrams Comparative Analysis Competitive Analysis Information Architecture **Navigation Systems** Organizational Research Personas Prototypes Rapid Ideation Research Methods Stakeholder Interviews Storyboards Test Planning **Usability Studies** User Flows User Interviews User Research **User Stories** Wireframes

Tools

Basecamp
Dropbox
Figma
Google Drive
Illustrator
Invision
Jira
Office 365
Optimal Workshop
Photoshop
Trello
ShareDrive
SharePoint
Sketch

Zoom